

# PERSONAL DETAILS:

Mobile: 519-113-460

**Email:** michal\_dabrowski@onet.eu

Linkedin profile:

www.linkedin.com/in/michał-dąbrowski-b67463120

GitHub profile:

https://github.com/m-dabrowsky

# **CERTIFICATES:**

- Language certificate B2 (Lodz University of Technology)
- Polish Electricians Association (SEP) certification -Inspection and Operation up to 1 kV
- Rework and Repair of Electronic Assemblies (RENEX ECC)
- ESD Control of Electronics Assembly (RENEX ECC)
- Cisco Certified Introduction to Cybersecurity (CISCO)
- Programming Essentials in Python (CISCO)
- Application and prototype development with QML and Qt5 (UDEMY)

# SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- Analytical and problem solving skills
- Good self-management
- Good time-management
- · Good communication and teamwork skills
- Reading technical documentations and electrical schematics
- Basic operation in Linux environment
- Familiarity with IDE's (Qt Creator, Visual Studio Code, STM32)
- Experience with GitHub
- Basic knowledge of CMake
- Basic knowledge of UML

#### Programming languages:

C++, Qt/QML, SQL, basics of Python

#### **Programs**

Eplan P8, Altium Designer, AutoCad, MicroStation PowerDraft

### Foreign languages:

English - B2, Spanish - A1

# MICHAŁ DĄBROWSKI

Highly self-motivated and goal-oriented engineer who wants to develop himself in embedded systems and programming cross-platform applications using the Qt framework.

Offers several years of experience demonstrating analytical and problem-solving skills in various fields and the ability to carry out projects from inception to completion.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

- ELECTRICAL DESIGN ENGINEER Revico SA, 08/2019-12/2020
- Creating project design and implementation of electrical solutions
- Creating necessary design reports
- Designing electrical systems for industrial facilities
- Conducting commissioning of electrical systems

#### AUTOMATIC ENGINEER TRAINEE

Mawos Sp. z o.o, 06/2018-02/2019

- · Resolving automation, electrical and instrumentation breakdowns
- Modification of electrical cabinets
- Creating and updating technical documentation for a new or existing projects
- Commissioning of industrial machines and devices

### • ELECTRONICS TECHNICIAN INTERN

Vitalis in Germany, 01/2013-02/2013

- · Leonardo da Vinci Programme
- Designing and building of an electric and solar powered vehicle

## **EDUCATION**

#### LODZ UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Master of Engineering, Project Management, 2020-present

- Using of Blockchain technology to improve business processes

#### LODZ UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Bachelor's Degree, Automatic Control and Robotics, 2015-2019

- Analog input circuit design for impedance measurement over wide frequency range

## HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Due to my enduring passion for engineering, I am interested in Blockchain technology, and the Internet of Things. I like to stay fit and go to the gym. I love hitchhiking and camper travel around the world, and in the evenings I love reading books about self-development.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).